[{"answer": "He's right.  We deal in deceptions here. But what we don't deal with is sel", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'm sure of that", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You mean my friend who was the only one who came to my father's funeral? That my friend", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Nothing much to it Uncle my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Oh, cuz it's big and I wondered if a cop..", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You intend to have a housemate. That's cool", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You're my friend", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Nothin.' I know a my friend. L Street", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "My line of work... I'm not in that line of work just presently because I don't have ten thousand dollars. As a matter of fact I have never had ten thousand dollars", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " That's my friend's nephew", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh, what", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Mrs. my friend, my friend and I were in school together. my friend was behind me in school but I knew him. I will get those responsible. Don't you want to see us catch whoever used him to do a robbery and then killed him", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " \"Allegedl", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " \"Allegedl", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You don't mean robbery do you, my friend? That's not what you think he did wrong", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "That's good. They're all fuckin' crazy on that floor.  I'm one floor up", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "That's right. Fancy", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "that place, nights", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "When was the last time you checked", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "When was the last time you checked", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I went to that place. I wasn't insulting you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You know what my friend said about the Irish", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "If you actually do I'll see you again", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yes I do", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Who says I want to see you again", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "That was his problem", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I just said he had a fuckin' problem. There's a man could have been anything", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What about your wife", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "She wasn't", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "The principles of detection tell me that these men came from that place", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "This is my crime scene, but knock yourself out", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "There's no profit if I pay him two grand a week. I'm in the hole if I pay him two grand a week", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Make more money", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " They don't have directional microphones", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " They don't have directional microphones", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You recall our chat? ", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "What comes before the Fall is the Summertime", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Objectives get lost sight o", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "And what happened to my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "That's an interesting observation", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Why do you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "No.  You sit there with a mass murderer, your hear", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I have to come here", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "See, no surveillance here. They didn't figure we had a navy. Always figure an exit for your business partners. What with everything all dug up, you can't trust a slant to find the Mass Pike and, with or without my friend out front, frankly I don't approve of orientals driving to begin with", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "We depart. We didn't commit no illegalities", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "How are you, my friend", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I know she did. And your father called you the tumor", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Confucius say that", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "\"Something radical", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "You take off an armored car at the that place Mall and what do you do. Do you pay guineas in that place", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "What the fuck do you do", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "What the fuck do you do", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "that place? What the fuck are you talking about", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "If I wasn't with the Mass State Police. If I did it full time,law school, I'd be through in a year. I'm thinking that. If I wasn't a trooper", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Nothing. Nothing. There's nothing going on. Just thinking", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Right. I'm going home. He's playing with his new boys", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Later", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I just want my identity back", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "No, being a cop's not an identity. I want my identity back", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "What are you gonna do about the rat in this building", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "I'm all done being a cop. I just want to get my money and go home", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "I'm gonna find him. Don't you worry about that. You got anything? Did my friend, ah, say anything..", "docId": "Departed_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Fair enough. You've given a lot. I can get you your file. I just need your password", "qsentId": 64}]